{
    "quiz":[
            {
                "question":"What is considered to be a personal information and should not be shared to the public?",
                "options":[
                    "Date of Birth",
                    "Address",
                    "Phone Number",
                    "All of the above"
                ],
                "answer":"All of the above"
            },
            {
                "question":"Your friend wants to use your email address to sign up for a website. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Share password to friend",
                    "No passwords are meant to be secret"
                ],
                "answer":"No passwords are meant to be secret"
            },
            {
                "question":"What is best password practice?",
                "options":[
                    "Use the same password for all accounts",
                    "Use a password that is easy to remember",
                    "Use a password that is hard to guess",
                    "Use a password that is easy to guess"
                ],
                "answer":"Use a password that is hard to guess"
            },
            {
                "question":"You are working on you laptop in a public, yet safe place and you need to leave for a few minutes. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Leave your laptop open",
                    "Lock your laptop",
                    "Turn off your laptop"
                ],
                "answer":"Lock your laptop"
            },
            {
                "question":"What is the best way to protect your computer from viruses?",
                "options":[
                    "Install an antivirus software",
                    "Don't use the internet",
                    "Don't use a computer"
                ],
                "answer":"Install an antivirus software"
            },
            {
                "question":"Your friend forwards an email to you containing a link to a website to download a free game. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Click on the link",
                    "Ignore the email",
                    "Ask your friend if the website is safe and prevent them from clicking on the link"
                ],
                "answer":"Ask your friend if the website is safe and prevent them from clicking on the link"
            },
            {
                "question":"You are in public place with free wifi. You want to enter your password to a secure account such as email or bank account. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Enter your password",
                    "Don't enter your password and wait until you get home",
                    "Enter your password but hide your screen"
                ],
                "answer":"Don't enter your password and wait until you get home"
            },
            {
                "question":"You get a message on social media from a famous superhero asking you to send money for a donation. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Send money",
                    "Ignore the message",
                    "Ask your friend if this is geniune",
                    "Ask a parent or guardian if the message is real"
                ],
                "answer":"Ask a parent or guardian if the message is real"
            },
            {
                "question":"What is a good way to create passwords?",
                "options":[
                    "Use your name as a password",
                    "Use a combination of letters, numbers, and symbols with length of 8 or more characters",
                    "Use a password that is easy to guess",
                    "Use your pets name as a password"
                ],
                "answer":"Use a combination of letters, numbers, and symbols with length of 8 or more characters"
            },
            {
                "question":"You are on a website and you see a pop-up that says you have won a free trip. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Click on the pop-up",
                    "Ignore the pop-up"
                ],
                "answer":"Ignore the pop-up"
            },
            {
                "question":"Your computer recently start running slow and low on disk space without downloading anything. You tried restarting the computer, but it did not help much. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Ignore the problem as it is normal",
                    "Delete some files to free up space",
                    "Ask a parent or guardian for help"
                ],
                "answer":"Ask a parent or guardian for help"
            },
            {
                "question":"What should you avoid while browsing the internet?",
                "options":[
                    "Clicking on pop-ups",
                    "Downloading files from unknown sources",
                    "Sharing personal information",
                    "All of the above"
                ],
                "answer":"All of the above"
            },
            {
                "question":"Which of the following is a definite way to confirm if a website is not secure?",
                "options":[
                    "The website has https:// in the URL",
                    "The website has a lock icon in the URL",
                    "The website has a warning sign in the URL",
                    "The website has a green checkmark in the URL"
                ],
                "answer":"The website has a warning sign in the URL"
            },
            {
                "question":"You see an ad that says the latest gaming console is on sale with 90% discount. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Click on the ad as you have been waiting for the console",
                    "Ignore the ad as it is too good to be true"
                ],
                "answer":"Ignore the ad as it is too good to be true"
            },
            {
                "question":"Who is responsible for your online safety?",
                "options":[
                    "Your parents",
                    "Your teachers",
                    "You",
                    "Your friends"
                ],
                "answer":"You"
            },
            {
                "question":"You can download any game you want from the internet if you have antivirus installed in your system.",
                "options":[
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ],
                "answer":"False"
            },
            {
                "question":"You should never share your password with anyone.",
                "options":[
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ],
                "answer":"True"
            },
            {
                "question":"You should always keep your computer updated with the latest software.",
                "options":[
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ],
                "answer":"True"
            },
            {
                "question":"You should always share your personal information with anyone who asks for it.",
                "options":[
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ],
                "answer":"False"
            },
            {
                "question":"You should always click on pop-ups that say you have won a prize.",
                "options":[
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ],
                "answer":"False"
            },
            {
                "question":"You are new to the social media network and you see a new game that predicts which car will you have in 5 years but asks for personal information. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Enter your personal information as the social media network is popular",
                    "Ignore the game"
                ],
                "answer":"Ignore the game"
            },
            {
                "question":"How can you protect your accounts in better way?",
                "options":[
                    "Use different passwords for different accounts",
                    "Use 2 factor authentication",
                    "Do not write down your passwords",
                    "All of the above"
                ],
                "answer":"All of the above"
            },
            {
                "question":"You get a SMS from an unknown number that says your package is delayed and click on the URL to confirm you still want the package. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Click on the URL as you ordered a package recently",
                    "Ignore the SMS",
                    "Check the account you ordered the package from and track the package from official website"
                ],
                "answer":"Check the account you ordered the package from and track the package from official website"
            },
            {
                "question":"Someone from your social media network asks for your address to send you a gift. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Share your address",
                    "Ask a parent or guardian if it is safe to share your address",
                    "Ignore the message"
                ],
                "answer":"Ask a parent or guardian if it is safe to share your address"
            },
            {
                "question":"Someone on your social media network is being mean to you. What should you do?",
                "options":[
                    "Be mean back",
                    "Ignore the person",
                    "Ask a parent or guardian for help"
                ],
                "answer":"Ask a parent or guardian for help"
            }
    ]
}